Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Volumes, flat shelving, oversize, and art
  - Folders Shelved Flat
    - Walton, William
      - Music/ Jubilate Deo, [1972] (Box 339, Folder 1976)
      - Music/ King Herod and the Cock, [1977] (Box 339, Folder 1977)
      - Music/ A Litany: score, 1916 (Box 339, Folder 1978)
      - Music/ Love Laid His Sleepless Head, 1918 Jul (Box 339, Folder 1979)
      - Music/ A Lyke-Wake Song, 1918 Jul (Box 339, Folder 1980)
      - Music/ March for A History of the English Speaking Peoples, [1959] (Box 339, Folder 1981)
      - Music/ Missa brevis, 1966 (Box 339, Folder 1982)
      - Music/ Passacaglia, violoncello, [1979-80?] (Box 339, Folder 1983)
      - Music/ Quartet, strings, no. 1: original folders, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 1984)
      - Music/ Salute to Sir Robert Mayer on His 100th Birthday, [1979] (Box 339, Folder 1985)
      - Music/ Sinfonia concertante, piano, orchestra: part for piano, [ca. 1943] (Box 340, Folder 1986)
      - Music/ A Song for the Lord Mayor's Table: short score, [1962] (Box 340, Folder 1987)
      - Music/ The Spitfire Prelude and Fugue: score, [1942-43] (Box 340, Folder 1988)
      - Music/ Symphony, no. 2: first movement, n.d. (Box 340, Folder 1989)
      - Music/ Title Music for BBC Shakespeare Series, [1977] (Box 340, Folder 1990)
      - Music/ Toccata, violin, piano, [1922-23] (Box 340, Folder 1991)
      - Music/ Tritons, 1920 (Box 340, Folder 1992)
      - Music/ The Twelve, 1965 (Box 340, Folder 1993)
    - Weber, Carl Maria von
      - Correspondence/Weber, Gottfried, 1811-15 (Box 341, Folder 1994-1996)
    - Wilde, Oscar
      - Writings/Other writings/"To L. L.", [ca. 1885] (Box 341, Folder 1997)
    - Wolf, Hugo
      - Music/ Goethe-Lieder, [1887] (Box 341, Folder 1998)
      - Music/ Ich stand in dunkeln Träumen, 1878 May 26-29 (Box 341, Folder 1999)
      - Music/ Mir träumte von einem Königskind, 1878 Jun 16 (Box 341, Folder 2000)
      - Music/ Wie des Mondes Abbild zittert, 1880 Feb 13 (Box 341, Folder 2001)
    - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno
      - Music/ Aria, violin, piano, 1900 Jul (Box 341, Folder 2002)
      - Music/ La bona mare, 1940 Aug 30 (Box 341, Folder 2003)
      - Music/ Canzone di Dante, 1897 Jun 4, n.d. (Box 341, Folder 2004)
      - Music/ Capriccio, piano, 1895 Nov (Box 342, Folder 2005)
      - Music/ Charfreitag, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 2006)
      - Music/ Concerto, violoncello, orchestra, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 2007)
      - Music/ Die drei Röselein, [early 1900s?] (Box 342, Folder 2008)
      - Music/ Frottola, [mid 1890s] (Box 342, Folder 2009)
      - Music/ Fugue, organ, 1904 Jul 14 (Box 342, Folder 2010)
      - Music/ Fugue, string quartet, [mid 1890s] (Box 342, Folder 2011)
      - Music/ Ghiribizzi quasi Ländler, 1895 Jun (Box 342, Folder 2012)
      - Music/ Larghetto, piano trio, [after 1900?] (Box 342, Folder 2013)
      - Music/ Mailied, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 2014)
      - Music/ Neig schöne Knospe, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 2015)
      - Music/ Passacaglia, organ, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 2016)
      - Music/ La passione, 1906 (Box 343, Folder 2017)
      - Music/ Pezzi, orchestra, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2018)
      - Music/ Pezzi, organ, 1895 Dec 14 (Box 343, Folder 2019)
      - Music/ Phantasietanz, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2020)
      - Music/ Prelude, piano, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2021)
      - Music/ Prelude and fugue, organ (Box 343, Folder 2022)
      - Music/ Quartet, strings, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2023)
      - Music/ Quartina; Stornello, [1890s?] (Box 343, Folder 2024)
      - Music/ Il riso, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2025)
      - Music/ Rispetti, op. 11, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2026)
      - Music/ Rispetti, op. 12, 1902 Oct 24 (Box 343, Folder 2027)
      - Music/ Scena di Orfeo, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 2028)
      - Music/ Il segreto di Susanna, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 2029)
      - Music/ Septet, piano, winds, strings (Box 344, Folder 2030)
      - Music/ Sextet, violins, violas, violoncellos: fourth movement, 1894 Oct (Box 344, Folder 2031)
      - Music/ Sextet, woodwinds, horn, 1900 Oct 29 (Box 344, Folder 2032)
      - Music/ Sonata, organ, [ca. 1900] (Box 344, Folder 2033)
      - Music/ Sonatas, piano, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 2034)
      - Music/ Sonata, violin, piano, A minor, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 2035)
      - Music/ Sonata, violin, piano, G minor, 1895 Jun (Box 344, Folder 2036)
      - Music/ Songs (1892), 1892 Dec 16 (Box 344, Folder 2037)
      - Music/ Songs (1896), 1896 Sep-Dec (Box 344, Folder 2038)
      - Music/ Songs (chorus), n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2039)
      - Music/ Suite-concertino, bassoon, string orchestra: drafts, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2040)
      - Music/ Suite-concertino, bassoon, string orchestra: arrangement for violin and string orchestra, [ca. 1933] (Box 345, Folder 2041)
      - Music/ Symphony, C major, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2042)
      - Music/ Symphony, E minor, 1894, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2043)
      - Music/ Symphony, F minor, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2044)
      - Music/ Symphony, F-sharp minor, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2045)
      - Music/ Totentanz, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2046)
      - Music/ Vom Berge, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2047)
      - Music/Unidentified/Fugue in E minor, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2048)
      - Music/Unidentified/Orchestra music, scherzo, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 2049)
      - Music/Unidentified/Orchestra music, theme and variations (Box 345, Folder 2050)
      - Music/Unidentified/Organ music, titled "Cantata 104, Bach", n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2051)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music in E minor, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2052)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music in five movements, [early 20th c?] (Box 346, Folder 2053)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music, theme and variations (Box 346, Folder 2054)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music in two movements, with sketches, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2055)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music, waltz, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2056)
      - Music/Unidentified/Piano music, waltzes, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2057)
      - Music/Exercises/"Auflösungen aus dem Mollakkord", 1928 Nov 20 (Box 346, Folder 2058)
      - Music/Exercises/"Bassschritte", n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2059)
      - Music/Exercises/Contrapuntal exercises, [early 1890s] (Box 346, Folder 2060)
      - Music/Exercises/Gluck, Paride ed Elena, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2061)
      - Music/Exercises/Rossini, Il barbiere di Siviglia, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 2062)
  - Oversize Folders
    - Burne-Jones, Edward Coley
      - Drawings/Illustrations for Archibald, Maclaren, The Fairy Family, n.d. (Box 347, Folder 2063-2066)
    - Cocteau, Jean
      - Writings/"En ce qui concerne les honneurs...", n.d. (Box Bsd, folder 2067)
    - Cox, Palmer
      - Drawings/ Brownie Calendar: 1893, January-March, [ca. 1893] (Box 348, Folder 2068-2070)
      - Drawings/ Brownie Calendar: 1893, April-June, [ca. 1893] (Box 349, Folder 2071-2073)
      - Drawings/ Brownie Calendar: 1893, July-September, [ca. 1893] (Box 350, Folder 2074-2076)
      - Drawings/ Brownie Calendar: 1893, October-December, [ca. 1893] (Box 351, Folder 2077-2079)
    - Hugo, Victor
      - Other Papers/Album relating to Victor Hugo, 1821-[70s], n.d. (Box 352, Folder 2080)
    - King, Jessie M.
      - Drawings/"And I will Give You a Coach and Six..." (Box 352, Folder 2081)
      - Drawings/"The Mermaid's Farewell", 1948 (Box 352, Folder 2082)
    - Maugham, Robin
      - Maugham Family Papers/Maugham, William/ Other papers, 1814 (Box Bsd, folder 2083)
    - Myers, Rollo H.
      - Other Papers/Arabic manuscript, n.d. (Box Bsd, folder 2084)
    - Proust, Marcel
      - Writings/ A l'ombre des jeunes filles en fleurs, n.d. (Box Bsd, folder 2085)
    - Shepard, Ernest H. (Ernest Howard)
      - Drawings/Milne, A. A., When We Were Very Young, n.d. (Box 353, Folder 2086-2094)
      - Drawings/Milne, A. A., When We Were Very Young, n.d. (Box 354, Folder 2095-2103)
      - Drawings/Milne, A. A., When We Were Very Young, n.d. (Box 355, Folder 2104-2112)
      - Drawings/Milne, A. A., When We Were Very Young, n.d. (Box 356, Folder 2113-2121)
      - Drawings/Milne, A. A., When We Were Very Young, n.d. (Box 357, Folder 2122-2128)
  - Art
    - Cocteau, Jean
      - Drawings/"Profile jaune", 1958 (Box (Art))
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 3, folder 58 (Box 358, Folder 2129)
  - Box 4, folder 79 (Box 358, Folder 2130)
  - Box 4, folder 89 (Box 358, Folder 2131)
  - Box 5, folder 95 (Box 358, Folder 2132)
  - Box 5, folder 124 (Box 358, Folder 2133)
  - Box 5, folder 131 (Box 358, Folder 2134)
  - Box 5, folder 138 (Box 358, Folder 2135)
  - Box 6, folder 148 (Box 358, Folder 2136)
  - Box 6, folder 156 (Box 358, Folder 2137)
  - Box 6, folder 158 (Box 358, Folder 2138)
  - Box 6, folder 160 (Box 358, Folder 2139)
  - Box 7, folder 187 (Box 358, Folder 2140)
  - Box 17, folder 267 (Box 358, Folder 2141)
  - Box 17, folder 268 (Box 358, Folder 2142)
  - Box 18, folder 279 (Box 358, Folder 2143)
  - Box 19, folder 300 (Box 358, Folder 2144)
  - Box 19, folder 306 (Box 358, Folder 2145)
  - Box 20, folder 360 (Box 358, Folder 2146)
  - Box 20, folder 377 (Box 358, Folder 2147)
  - Box 20, folder 379 (Box 358, Folder 2148)
  - Box 20, folder 382 (Box 358, Folder 2149)
  - Box 21, folder 384 (Box 358, Folder 2150)
  - Box 21, folder 414 (Box 358, Folder 2151)
  - Box 22, folder 429 (Box 358, Folder 2152)
  - Box 22, folder 463 (Box 358, Folder 2153)
  - Box 23, folder 465 (Box 358, Folder 2154)
  - Box 23, folder 467 (Box 358, Folder 2155)
  - Box 23, folder 472 (Box 358, Folder 2156)
  - Box 23, folder 483 (Box 358, Folder 2157)
  - Box 23, folder 485 (Box 358, Folder 2158)
  - Box 23, folder 486 (Box 358, Folder 2159)
  - Box 23, folder 489 (Box 358, Folder 2160)
  - Box 23, folder 490 (Box 358, Folder 2161)
  - Box 24, folder 499 (Box 358, Folder 2162)
  - Box 24, folder 501 (Box 358, Folder 2163)
  - Box 24, folder 503 (Box 358, Folder 2164)
  - Box 24, folder 505 (Box 358, Folder 2165)
  - Box 24, folder 527 (Box 358, Folder 2166)
  - Box 25, folder 556 (Box 358, Folder 2167)
  - Box 25, folder 557 (Box 358, Folder 2168)
  - Box 26, folder 580 (Box 358, Folder 2169)
  - Box 26, folder 584 (Box 358, Folder 2170)
  - Box 26, folder 587 (Box 358, Folder 2171)
  - Box 26, folder 590 (Box 358, Folder 2172)
  - Box 27, folder 591 (Box 358, Folder 2173)
  - Box 27, folder 594 (Box 358, Folder 2174)
  - Box 27, folder 600 (Box 358, Folder 2174a)
  - Box 28, folder 604 (Box 359, Folder 2175)
  - Box 28, folder 605 (Box 359, Folder 2176)
  - Box 28, folder 617 (Box 359, Folder 2177)
  - Box 28, folder 621 (Box 359, Folder 2178)
  - Box 30, folder 655 (Box 359, Folder 2179)
  - Box 31, folder 662 (Box 359, Folder 2180)
  - Box 31, folder 667 (Box 359, Folder 2181)
  - Box 31, folder 671 (Box 359, Folder 2182)
  - Box 31, folder 672 (Box 359, Folder 2183)
  - Box 31, folder 675 (Box 359, Folder 2184)
  - Box 32, folder 677 (Box 359, Folder 2185)
  - Box 32, folder 682 (Box 359, Folder 2186)
  - Box 32, folder 684 (Box 359, Folder 2187)
  - Box 33, folder 692 (Box 359, Folder 2188)
  - Box 33, folder 697 (Box 359, Folder 2189)
  - Box 33, folder 700 (Box 359, Folder 2190)
  - Box 33, folder 702 (Box 359, Folder 2191)
  - Box 34, folder 706 (Box 359, Folder 2192)
  - Box 34, folder 708 (Box 359, Folder 2193)
  - Box 34, folder 711 (Box 359, Folder 2194)
  - Box 34, folder 716 (Box 359, Folder 2195)
  - Box 34, folder 717 (Box 359, Folder 2196)
  - Box 34, folder 718 (Box 359, Folder 2197)
  - Box 34, folder 719 (Box 359, Folder 2198)
  - Box 35, folder 722 (Box 359, Folder 2199)
  - Box 35, folder 728 (Box 359, Folder 2200)
  - Box 36, folder 738 (Box 359, Folder 2201)
  - Box 36, folder 739 (Box 359, Folder 2202)
  - Box 36, folder 749 (Box 359, Folder 2203)
  - Box 36, folder 750 (Box 360, Folder 2204)
  - Box 37, folder 751 (Box 360, Folder 2205)
  - Box 37, folder 752 (Box 360, Folder 2206)
  - Box 37, folder 753 (Box 360, Folder 2207)
  - Box 37, folder 754 (Box 360, Folder 2208)
  - Box 39, folder 791 (Box 360, Folder 2209)
  - Box 42, folder 855 (Box 360, Folder 2210)
  - Box 43, folder 861 (Box 360, Folder 2211)
  - Box 43, folder 862 (Box 360, Folder 2212)
  - Box 43, folder 863 (Box 360, Folder 2213)
  - Box 43, folder 878 (Box 360, Folder 2214)
  - Box 43, folder 879 (Box 360, Folder 2215)
  - Box 45, folder 896 (Box 360, Folder 2216)
  - Box 45, folder 897 (Box 360, Folder 2217)
  - Box 45, folder 909 (Box 360, Folder 2218)
  - Box 43, folder 914 (Box 360, Folder 2219)
  - Box 45, folder 918 (Box 360, Folder 2220)
  - Box 45, folder 919 (Box 360, Folder 2221)
  - Box 45, folder 920 (Box 360, Folder 2222)
  - Box 46, folder 928 (Box 360, Folder 2223)
  - Box 46, folder 930 (Box 360, Folder 2224)
  - Box 47, folder 955 (Box 360, Folder 2225)
  - Box 47, folder 956 (Box 360, Folder 2226)
  - Box 47, folder 958 (Box 360, Folder 2227)
  - Box 47, folder 959 (Box 360, Folder 2228)
  - Box 48, folder 969 (Box 360, Folder 2229)
  - Box 48, folder 978 (Box 360, Folder 2230)
  - Box 48, folder 980 (Box 360, Folder 2231)
  - Box 48, folder 989 (Box 360, Folder 2232)
  - Box 48, folder 998 (Box 360, Folder 2233)
  - Box 49, folder 1009 (Box 360, Folder 2234)
  - Box 49, folder 1033 (Box 360, Folder 2235)
  - Box 49, folder 1034 (Box 360, Folder 2236)
  - Box 49, folder 1036 (Box 360, Folder 2237)
  - Box 49, folder 1042 (Box 360, Folder 2238)
  - Box 49, folder 1046 (Box 360, Folder 2239)
  - Box 50, folder 1049 (Box 360, Folder 2240)
  - Box 50, folder 1051 (Box 360, Folder 2241)
  - Box 50, folder 1057 (Box 360, Folder 2242)
  - Box 50, folder 1059 (Box 360, Folder 2243)
  - Box 50, folder 1060 (Box 361, Folder 2244)
  - Box 50, folder 1061 (Box 361, Folder 2245)
  - Box 50, folder 1063 (Box 361, Folder 2246)
  - Box 50, folder 1064 (Box 361, Folder 2247)
  - Box 50, folder 1065 (Box 361, Folder 2248)
  - Box 50, folder 1066 (Box 361, Folder 2249)
  - Box 50, folder 1068 (Box 361, Folder 2250)
  - Box 51, folder 1077 (Box 361, Folder 2251)
  - Box 51, folder 1079 (Box 361, Folder 2252)
  - Box 51, folder 1081 (Box 361, Folder 2253)
  - Box 51, folder 1083 (Box 361, Folder 2254)
  - Box 51, folder 1084 (Box 361, Folder 2255)
  - Box 51, folder 1085 (Box 361, Folder 2256)
  - Box 51, folder 1093 (Box 361, Folder 2257)
  - Box 51, folder 1094 (Box 361, Folder 2258)
  - Box 51, folder 1097 (Box 361, Folder 2259)
  - Box 51, folder 1099 (Box 361, Folder 2260)
  - Box 52, folder 1113 (Box 361, Folder 2261)
  - Box 52, folder 1116 (Box 361, Folder 2262)
  - Box 52, folder 1117 (Box 361, Folder 2263)
  - Box 52, folder 1120 (Box 361, Folder 2264)
  - Box 52, folder 1122 (Box 361, Folder 2265)
  - Box 52, folder 1123 (Box 361, Folder 2266)
  - Box 52, folder 1124 (Box 361, Folder 2267)
  - Box 52, folder 1127 (Box 361, Folder 2268)
  - Box 52, folder 1128 (Box 361, Folder 2269)
  - Box 52, folder 1129 (Box 361, Folder 2270)
  - Box 52, folder 1130 (Box 361, Folder 2271)
  - Box 53, folder 1135 (Box 361, Folder 2272)
  - Box 53, folder 1136 (Box 361, Folder 2273)
  - Box 53, folder 1140 (Box 361, Folder 2274)
  - Box 53, folder 1142 (Box 361, Folder 2275)
  - Box 53, folder 1148 (Box 361, Folder 2276)
  - Box 53, folder 1149 (Box 361, Folder 2277)
  - Box 53, folder 1150 (Box 361, Folder 2278)
  - Box 53, folder 1151 (Box 361, Folder 2279)
  - Box 54, folder 1180 (Box 361, Folder 2280)
  - Box 54, folder 1183 (Box 361, Folder 2281)
  - Box 54, folder 1187 (Box 361, Folder 2282)
  - Box 54, folder 1188 (Box 361, Folder 2283)
  - Box 54, folder 1192 (Box 361, Folder 2284)
  - Box 55, folder 1200 (Box 361, Folder 2285)
  - Box 55, folder 1209 (Box 361, Folder 2286)
  - Box 57, folder 1248 (Box 361, Folder 2287)
  - Box 57, folder 1264 (Box 361, Folder 2288)
  - Box 57, folder 1283 (Box 361, Folder 2289)
  - Box 58, folder 1329 (Box 361, Folder 2290)
  - Box 59, folder 1367 (Box 361, Folder 2291)
  - Box 59, folder 1368 (Box 361, Folder 2292)
  - Box 59, folder 1369 (Box 361, Folder 2293)
  - Box 59, folder 1372 (Box 361, Folder 2294)
  - Box 60, folder 1379 (Box 361, Folder 2295)
  - Box 60, folder 1384 (Box 361, Folder 2296)
  - Box 61, folder 1391 (Box 361, Folder 2297)
  - Box 61, folder 1393 (Box 361, Folder 2298)
  - Box 323, folder 1756 (Box 361, Folder 2299)
  - Box 336, folder 1950 (Box 361, Folder 2300)
- Restricted Fragile Oversize
  - Box 46, folder 929 (Box 362, Folder 2301)
  - Box 336, folder 1949 (Box 362, Folder 2302)
  - Box 340, folder 1993 (Box 362, Folder 2303)